I do love uh traveling. I get to travel
a lot with this job. I just got back
from my hometown. I was down in uh
Louisiana. You got
any That's No, it's fine. That's how I
feel about it, too. Just kind
of difficult hard times where I love
going to Louisiana, though, y'all, cuz I
stay with my nana when I'm down there. I
love my nana, y'all. She is 88 years
old. the coolest lady I have ever met. I
love hanging out with her. And the
reason it's so much fun to hang out with
her now is because about 10 years ago
when my papa died, she took all the
money he left her and she started
pimping out her house, right? Like
making her crib nice. She has a bad
back, so she put a big old hot tub on a
deck right there in the yard. Uh she
doesn't have any of her real teeth left.
Uh so her refrigerator is always full of
pudding cups.
Thank you, Nana. And
uh and she has the biggest TV I've ever
seen. I'm not kidding, y'all. They gave
this old woman one inch of TV for every
year she's been alive. It's huge. It's
really
big. And if she is awake, the TV is on.
And she keeps the TV tuned to the game
show
network. And her favorite show is Family
Feud.
Y'all, we watched it every day I was
there. And I'm not kidding you. We were
up late one afternoon. It was like
3:30 and we could not take our eyes off
this particular episode, y'all, cuz the
families were tied. The families were
tied. The point value is tripled. Top
three answers are on the board. Name
something you put on a baked potato. My
nana stands up and screams, "Aluminum
foil.
[Applause]
[Laughter]
She's not wrong. She's not
wrong. But when the number one answer
was butter, push, she's
mad. When answers two and three were
sour cream and chives, she lost it right
there in the living room. She stood up.
I have been making baked potatoes since
1952.
I've made them without butter. I've made
them without sour cream. I'm not
entirely sure what the heck a chive even
is, but I had never in my life made a
baked potato for
you. And then she just got up and turned
the TV off and went to bed. She was done
with all of us.
She doesn't like my phone, my cell
phone, cuz it makes too many noises,
right? She calls it my bing bong. She's
like, "Jennifer, your bing bong is bing
bonging. Come get your bing
bong." She doesn't even know what it's
called, but she wants to know who it is.
Right. What? Why is it bing bonging?
It's just an email, Nana. Who's it
from? Um, the electric company. What are
they saying?
Well, I owe him
$183,
so I might just stay here for an extra
couple days if that's
[Laughter]
okay. The best part about staying at
Nana's house is come 6:00
p.m. I got the whole place to myself,
right? She takes a pill at 5:30 and goes
night night. I'm in the hot tub with a
pudding cup like I love Nana. This is
delicious. I almost got I almost got in
trouble though cuz she she said to me,
she said, "What is it you do when I go
to
bed?" I mean, I'm not going to lie to my
nana. So, I was like,
"Well, I've been eating copious amounts
of pudding in the hot
tub." She's like, "Oh,
baby, that's not good for you. That heat
and all that milk
I said, "Well, I'm not doing that
tonight, Nana. It's my last night here,
and tonight I just see that they're
running a marathon of this TV show I've
been wanting to see. So, I'm going to
get some pudding cups and sit in front
of the TV and just watch watch my show."
And she says, "Well, it's your last
night here, so I tell you what,
tonight I'm not going to take my pill.
I'm gonna stay up and watch TV with
you."
Ain't that
sweet? I was like,
"Wow, what are you going to do with that
pill?" So, we got some pudding
cups. We sat in front of the TV. Now,
the TV show I was dying to see at the
time was The People Versus OJ Simpson,
right? That was a very big deal when I
was a young kid. I mean, we'd never seen
reality TV at that point. You know what
I mean? That was crazy for us. But we
were getting to look at our first
Kardashian, right? We didn't know what
that was going to turn into, did we?
Nobody Nobody could have foreseen that.
It was crazy. And I loved it. I was so
addicted to it when it was happening in
real life. And so, I really wanted to
see this, you know, reenactment of it.
And after about three episodes, I
realized that Nana does not remember
that this happened the first
time because she says to me after
episode three, she
goes, "You know
what? I bet you that Mark Ferman guy
turns out to be
racist." I was like, I think you're
right. And I saw an
opportunity. So, I bet my nana $183 that
they find OJ not
guilty. She took that bet and that's how
I paid my electric bill. That's
right. Don't get upset. She's my nana.
She'd want me to have lights. It's okay.